[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2001, NASA sent this unmanned spacecraft to orbit Mars in search of signs of water and volcanic activity on the surface.", "correct_answer": "Mars Odyssey", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars Exploration Rover", "Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter", "Mars Pathfinder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Baroque period of architecture is characterized by vivid colours, luxurious materials and elaborate surface textures. Which of these buildings is an example of typical Baroque architecture?", "correct_answer": "St Peter\u2019s Basilica", "incorrect_answers": ["The Royal Scottish Academy", "Solitude Palace", "Lincoln Memorial"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Disney movie are the following lines from: In every job that must be done, there is an element of fun. You find the fun, and - SNAP - the jobs a game!?", "correct_answer": "Mary Poppins", "incorrect_answers": ["The Rescuers Down Under", "Toy Story", "Sleeping Beauty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Irish hero,spurred on by the French Revolution, is widely regarded as the father of Irish republicans.", "correct_answer": "Wolfe Tone", "incorrect_answers": ["Patrick McCormack", "Brian Clohessy", "Kevin  ODoul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the iPod Shuffle come out?", "correct_answer": "none of these", "incorrect_answers": ["August 2004", "December 2002", "April 2003"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The hummingbird is the worlds smallest bird.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which US President signed the law, which established the Congressional Medal of Honor - the highest military decoration awarded by the United States?", "correct_answer": "Lincoln", "incorrect_answers": ["Grant", "A. Johnson", "John Adams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ichthyology is the study of biting insects such a fleas, mosquitoes and wasps.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which countrys diamonds were the first ones banned as conflict (or blood) diamonds by the UN?", "correct_answer": "Angolas", "incorrect_answers": ["South Africas", "Mozambiques", "Sierra Leones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the only B vitamin that cannot be obtained from plant products?", "correct_answer": "B12", "incorrect_answers": ["B7", "B1", "B6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies was the first box-office success for director Francis Ford Coppola since Apocalypse Now?", "correct_answer": "Peggy Sue Got Married", "incorrect_answers": ["The Godfather Part III", "The Mosquito Coast", "The Outsiders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the star at the center of the Solar System called by the Romans?", "correct_answer": "Sol", "incorrect_answers": ["Helios", "Aredid", "Sun"]}]